welcome to a short video about STS for
欢迎收看有关STS的简短视频
remote duffels client featured have a
特色的远程行李客户端
toy project in my workspace
我的工作区中的玩具项目
this project has dev tools on it and
这个专案有开发工具
have deployed this project with a cloud
用云部署了这个项目
foundry and the app is up and running
铸造和应用程序已启动并正在运行
now let's try and attach your death
现在让我们尝试附加你的死亡
tolls climb to it I do it by
通行费攀升至
right-clicking on the ACF app in the
右键点击
blue dashboards fine and click on must
蓝色的仪表板很好，然后单击必须
restart a more deathless client menu
重新启动更致命的客户端菜单
item in that set right so behind the
该项目中的正确位置，因此
scenes it's amoled secrets are set up
设置了令人讨厌的场景
for you remote app and local and
为您的远程应用程序和本地
communication for the you know was a
你所知道的沟通是
remote death of a deathless client and
死忠客户的远程死亡，以及
the remote app has is being set up
正在设置远程应用
behind the scenes here you need to worry
这里的幕后您需要担心
about any of it so they we can sell that
关于其中的任何东西，以便我们可以出售
remote Deadpool's client has been
远程Deadpool的客户端已经
attached to the app already by looking
通过查看已附加到应用程序
this DT at the bottom of the icon it's
该DT位于图标底部
been it was fast because it's not the
因为它不是
first time I attached a remote doubles
我第一次附上遥控双打
client to this app if you touch it for
如果您触摸此应用程序的客户端
the first time it's gonna take a while
第一次需要一段时间
because of course for redeployment is
因为当然是重新部署
going to be done because new environment
因为新环境而要做
variables sir edits so remote death
变量先生编辑，所以远程死亡
tolls client has been touched and I can
收费客户感动了，我可以
try change things in our application
尝试在我们的应用程序中进行更改
locally and see if remote app picks it
在本地查看是否由远程应用选择
up so we have this request mapping and
向上，所以我们有此请求映射，
point hi so if we look at it it says the
嗨，所以如果我们看一下它说
message hi right so we can change that
消息您好，我们可以更改
message to hello and see if a mote
留言给你好，看看是否有微粒
Ethel's client makes the change is
埃塞尔的客户做出的改变是
possible yeah we can sell from the log
是的，我们可以从原木上出售
classes and updates and reload has has
类，更新和重新加载具有
been done ray so quick look at the page
ray完成后，请快速浏览页面
it says hello now we can try and add a
它说你好，我们可以尝试添加一个
new request mapping let's say it's going
我们说新的请求映射
to be request mapping by now so by put
现在是请求映射，因此放置
the mappings boy for the methods and boy
方法和男孩的映射男孩
for the message
对于消息
save it let's see if remote dev tools
保存一下，看看是否有远程开发工具
client will propagate the change
客户将传播更改
No so you see this green marker has
否，所以您看到此绿色标记具有
appeared around the annotation that
出现在注释附近
means the request mapping is a life now
意味着请求映射已经成为现实
right and this is the light request
对，这是轻要求
mapping URL it's a just says by rain you
映射URL这只是一个小雨而已
can also change stuff on the application
也可以更改应用程序上的内容
properties because it's also in the
属性，因为它也在
class path so we have a banner mode
类路径，所以我们有横幅模式
console right so we see spring butter
正确的控制台，所以我们看到春天黄油
here somewhere yeah right here you
在这里，是的，就在这里，你
change it to off we won't see the
将其更改为关闭，我们将不会看到
spawner winding up restarts okay so the
产卵器清盘可以重新启动，所以
file water does restart right then we
文件水确实重新启动，然后我们
didn't see the banner month wasn't
没有看到标语月份不是
restarted we put the banner back the
重新启动，我们将横幅放回
console save it
控制台保存
we'll see it now no yeah you saw the
现在，我们将看到它，是的，您看到了
banner right there it's great
横幅就在那很棒
ok so we can do the touch removal to
好的，我们可以进行触摸去除
death to describe you find any console
死亡来形容你找到任何控制台
and you press this generate button and
然后按此生成按钮，然后
that kills three more death tolls client
杀死了三个死亡人数的客户
app and DG's contact man sets
app和DG的联络人集
disconnected so that's it that's the
断开连接，就是这样
remote deftness client feature in SDS
SDS中的远程灵巧客户端功能
for thank you for watching
感谢您的收看
you
您